<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018 on Skyview Stormbots</title>
    <link>/seasons/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018 on Skyview Stormbots</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/seasons/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>District Championship Availability</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/districtchampionshipavailablity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/districtchampionshipavailablity/</guid>
      <description>We have mathematically qualified for the District Championships in Portland next week, April 4-7. We are currently aware of the following students who cannot attend:
 Alex Alina Jessica V. Joe V. Kristen Maia Ryan W. Terik WIlliam  If you are not on this list, but cannot attend, please email me ASAP.
Thanks,
 Mr. Glassett
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting For Potential Houston Travelers</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/houstontravelmeetingtuesdaynight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/houstontravelmeetingtuesdaynight/</guid>
      <description>This email was sent to your parents:
 Parents – if you are even considering your student going to the FIRST World Championships in Houston with the Stormbots in April, you must attend the parent meeting this Tuesday night at 6:30. We are planning to make committed reservations as soon as Wednesday, so we need your attendance so you understand the costs and other requirements. I know there has already been a note about this, but we really need everyone who is interested in their child going to Houston to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Gear From Competitions</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/spiritgearfromyakima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/spiritgearfromyakima/</guid>
      <description>If you accidentally brought home spirit gear from the Yakima (Sun Dome) or Oregon City (Clackamas Academy) competitions, please remember to bring them back to robotics practice tonight. If you cannot bring it tonight please email me back with what you have so I can have a running inventory of this year’s spirit gear. Mrs. Snyder worked hard making all those costumes alongside marketing so we would relay appreciate it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Schedule Changes - Week Of March 25th</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/practiceschedulechangesthisweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/practiceschedulechangesthisweek/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve had a great season so far – let’s keep it going by doing well at Lake Oswego! The practice plan for this week has changed a bit – please read below. As always, any emails you get after this that come from your mentors take precedent over this post.
Monday  ONLY Programming is practicing. 6:00 to 9:00 (may run a little late) Unbag #1 – Programming Get the new code debugged Work on auto improvements  Tuesday  All Team meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Yakima</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/-date-celebratingyakima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/-date-celebratingyakima/</guid>
      <description>Tonight we want to celebrate the Yakima district competition. I would like to give students and mentors an opportunity to share some of their highlights. This is a heads up in case you have something you would like to share, you will have the opportunity tonight. You do not need to let me know ahead of time, but when you do share, try to keep it under a minute and be positive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>