<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Skyview Stormbots</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Skyview Stormbots</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Parent Meeting, March 6 at 6:15pm</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/travelparentmeetingmarch6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/travelparentmeetingmarch6/</guid>
      <description>This note is a reminder of a critical parent meeting Tuesday night at 6:30 pm for the parents of Stormbots who are traveling (see below) to Yakima on March 15-17. This meeting will cover details of the travel plan, get required forms completed and signed by parents, and collect student travel fees for hotels, etc. Please bring a checkbook. Please let us know any questions.
The normal all team StormBot meeting will happen at 6:00 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Back, and Looking Forward</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/lookingbacklookingforward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/lookingbacklookingforward/</guid>
      <description>What a way to start the year! Fantastic first competition that sets us up very well for the future. There were lots of highlights; but to me a day later what comes through so well is how much of a total team effort it was. From robot performance to team spirit/appearance to parent/friend support to safety performance to consistent Gracious Professionalism – you did it all!
While keeping the great feeling of success, it’s now time for us to think about future competitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer Opportunity, March 20</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/volunteeropportunitymarch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/volunteeropportunitymarch/</guid>
      <description>How are you sharing the values of First? Here is another opportunity to pay it forward.
 STEM &amp;ldquo;Boost&amp;rdquo; club at Harney is scheduled to get underway on Tuesday, March 20 from 3:00-4:00pm after-school. The club will run for 8 weeks (except for Spring break April 3) and will be a series of work sessions with adult and high school (hopefully) volunteers working with individual students in a classroom setting to assist them in their various projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Performance at Clackamas Academy!</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/amazingpreformance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/amazingpreformance/</guid>
      <description>What an amazing weekend and performance at the CAIS district event! We finished the qualification rounds with a record of 10-2 and were the third-seeded robot out of 37. We then became the second alliance captain, and along with the help of Apex Robotics (5803) and Beavertronics (5970), we made it all the way to the finals, where we lost to an outstanding alliance. We then earned both the Safety Award and the Quality Award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One Short Recap, Clackamas Academy, 2018</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/dayonerecapclackamas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/dayonerecapclackamas/</guid>
      <description>What an amazing first day! We finished 7-2 and are currently 4th out of 37 teams.
Here is a link to one of our better matches today: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KwlfWlRGb9M
Students need to be at Skyview by 6:30 a.m. Saturday morning.
Go StormBots!
 Mr. Glassett
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Competition Update</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/saturdayupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/saturdayupdate/</guid>
      <description>Departure from the school went well this morning. We are on the bus now and ahead of schedule. If you want to follow our team today, here is the best way to do so: https://www.thebluealliance.com/event/2018orore
We hope to be back to school by 9:45-10:00 tonight. However, it may run late. Hopefully, there isn&amp;rsquo;t an accident that closes down the 205 bridge like last year :)
Tomorrow morning we will leave a little later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Jackets, 2018</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/teamjackets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/teamjackets/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately, the weather last week set our screen/printer back and we will not have jackets until Saturday morning. You will be able to get them when you arrive on Saturday morning.
Sorry for the inconvenience,
 Mr. Glassett
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clackamas Academy Information From Team Meeting</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/-missinglinks-clackamasacademyinformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/-missinglinks-clackamasacademyinformation/</guid>
      <description>I have linked the schedules I sent the other day. I have also linked the slides we covered tonight. In those slides are greater details about student specific roles and expectations at the competitions. For those of you who just want the critical times for our team, I have listed them below.
Day 1: Thursday 3&amp;frasl;1  3:00 p.m. Carpool departs Skyview 5:00 p.m. Pits Open 9:00 p.m. Pits Close 10:00 Return Skyview  Day 2: Friday 3&amp;frasl;2  6:15 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clackamas Academy District Schedule</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/-missinglinks-clackamasacademydistrictschedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/-missinglinks-clackamasacademydistrictschedule/</guid>
      <description>I will be sending out more student specific information after I cover it tomorrow in our all-team meeting, but wanted to send our schedule now since a few people have asked for them. Linked below, you will find:
 CAIS StormBots Schedule: This one is specific to our team and includes bus departure and arrival times. Please recognize that our bus arrival times at the end of the day are dependent on the schedule of the tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Status Update, February 25, 2018</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/weeklystatusupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/weeklystatusupdate/</guid>
      <description>This week saw the completion of the Build Season and the beginning of the Competition Season! It is an exciting time, with more to come! We have a working robot, and will spend this week making it even better before heading to our first competition later this week in Clackamas/Oregon City! Very nice job, Stormbots!
Below I summarize the week’s agenda, with more details afterwards. Please read through the entire note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer Opportunity, January 16</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/volunteeropportunityjanuary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/volunteeropportunityjanuary/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity for StormBots to volunteer to help with FIRST LEGO Leauge ad FIRST Tech Challenge:
Dear FIRST LEGO League Oregon Community:
Congratulations on a exciting Hydro Dynamics season! I&amp;rsquo;m Cathy Swider, FIRST Tech Challenge Oregon Programs Manager for ORTOP.
With the conclusion of our FIRST LEGO League Oregon Qualifying Events and the State Championship this past weekend, some FIRST LEGO League teams or FIRST LEGO League team members, may be looking for the next FIRST program challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNAP Fundraiser Update!</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/snapfundraiserupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/snapfundraiserupdate/</guid>
      <description>We have raised $3220 already through our SNAP fundraiser! This is outstanding! Keep up the good work. You may be thinking, &amp;ldquo;No, we have raised $4600.&amp;rdquo; You are correct, but we actually keep 70% of what we raise. The other 30% goes to SNAP to keep their business running. If you are upset by this, recognize that most fundraisers only allow you to keep 40-50% of the profit. The Payback books cost our program $10 a book a few years ago and we sold them for $20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GameSense</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/-emailnotloaded-gamesense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/-emailnotloaded-gamesense/</guid>
      <description>CONTENT MISSING</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Week of Build Season!</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/-emailnotloaded-weekoneofbuildseason/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/-emailnotloaded-weekoneofbuildseason/</guid>
      <description>CONTENT MISSING</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Final FIRST Blog before the GAME REVEAL!</title>
      <link>/posts/2018/-emailnotloaded-finalfirstblogbeforegamereveal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018/-emailnotloaded-finalfirstblogbeforegamereveal/</guid>
      <description>CONTENT MISSING</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSVP For The 2017-2018 Stormbots&#39; Showcase</title>
      <link>/posts/2012/12-02-rsvp-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2012/12-02-rsvp-showcase/</guid>
      <description>The StormBots&amp;rsquo; Showcase is scheduled for Thursday, February 8, 2018 from 7:00 - 9:00 p.m. at Skyview High School. To RSVP, click here and fill out the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stormbots Team List for 2017-2018</title>
      <link>/posts/2017/10-11-team-announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2017/10-11-team-announcements/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to everyone that applied to be on the team and attended our Skills Assessment last Tuesday. Our first official all-team meeting is Tuesday, October 3rd, from 6-9pm in the 600 Wing. Enter through the 600 wing side door. The front doors to the school will not be open.
For a description of sub-teams, click on this link: About The Stormbots.
For questions, please contact one of our coaches: Luke Glassett or Kurt Schmidt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2017 - Important Dates</title>
      <link>/posts/2017/09-01-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2017/09-01-dates/</guid>
      <description> Girls Generation Practice Saturday, September 30 from 9:00 a.m. - 11:00 a.m. Wednesday, October 4 from 8:00 p.m. - 8:00 p.m.
First StormBots Team Meeting Tuesday, October 3, 6:00 p.m.
Parent/Student Meeting Tuesday, October 10, 6:00 p.m.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competition Updates for the 2017 Season</title>
      <link>/posts/2017/competitionupdates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2017/competitionupdates/</guid>
      <description>Competition Updates for the 2017 Season Pacific Northwest Championships in Cheney, WA, April 6-8, 2017 The team left on Wednesday of Spring Break and drove to Cheney with our awesome bus driver Kelly. We passed inspection and set up our pit Wednesday night, and qualification matches started Thursday afternoon. Blue Thunder put in a valiant effort and ended up ranking as the #34 robot out of 64. Unfortunately, we were not selected for elimination rounds but enjoyed cheering on other teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stormbots Team List for 2016-2017</title>
      <link>/posts/2016/10-12-team-announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016/10-12-team-announcements/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to everyone that applied to be on the team and attended our Skills Assessment on Monday Night. Our first official all-team meeting is Wednesday, 10/12/16 from 6-9pm in the 600 Wing. Enter through the 600 wing side door. The front doors to the school will not be open.
For a description of sub-teams, click on this link: About The Stormbots.
For questions, please contact one of our coaches: Luke Glassett, Kurt Schmidt, or Kim Hansen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Events</title>
      <link>/posts/2016/09-22-upcoming-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016/09-22-upcoming-events/</guid>
      <description>Tonight Make sure you have signed-in.
Girls - if you want to participate in Girls Generation on Oct 15, sign-up on that sheet too.
Potential mentors - Please fill out a Mentor Interest sheet.
All are Strongly encouraged to complete the application tonight. Link can be found on our website at www.stormbots.com.
Wednesday, September 28th, 6PM - Girls only First Girls Generation Practice Enter through the 600 wing door Additional practices times to be determined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stormbot Sub-Team Descriptions</title>
      <link>/posts/2016/10-5-subteam-descriptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016/10-5-subteam-descriptions/</guid>
      <description>Logistics Team This team is responsible for team budget, inventory control, robot parts organization and ordering, and event logistics (ie competitions). It is an excellent fit for someone looking to learn business skills as well as some technical skills.
Marketing Team This team is responsible for managing our team image and getting the word out about us through social and traditional media. It is an excellent fit for someone looking to learn or use their marketing and business skills in a real life application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We won a blue banner!</title>
      <link>/posts/2016/07-21-blue-banner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016/07-21-blue-banner/</guid>
      <description>After five hours of watching our robots battle it out, we traversed our way in victory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WINNERS 2016 PHILOMATH COMPETITION!</title>
      <link>/posts/2016/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016/text/</guid>
      <description> WINNERS 2016 PHILOMATH COMPETITION! This weekend, the StormBots won:  Philomath Competition
 Quality Award sponsored by Motorola Solutions Foundation
 Industrial Safety Award sponsored by Underwriters Laboratories
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:50:38 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Skyview Stormbots: 2811  FRC Team 2811 StormBots calls Skyview High School it&#39;s home base. Skyview is the Science, Mathematics and Technology (SMT) magnet of the Vancouver Public Schools and is a certified Project Lead The Way: Pathway to Engineering high school. The team meets at Skyview High School 1300 NW 139th St., Vancouver, WA 98685. All are welcome to visit us but please contact us first about your plans since our schedule varies based on seasonal events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press Fitting Bearings with Dry Ice</title>
      <link>/posts/2016/02-14-bearing-press-fit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016/02-14-bearing-press-fit/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kickoff!</title>
      <link>/posts/2016/01-09-kickoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016/01-09-kickoff/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Season Clock</title>
      <link>/posts/2015/2015-01-03-build-season-clock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2015/2015-01-03-build-season-clock/</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the 2015 kickoff, we unveil our new invention: A build season clock. This clock is precisely gear to make 1 turn over a 6 week period. When the clock strikes midnight, it&amp;rsquo;s time to bag the robot and pack it in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRC Kickoff - Saturday, January 3, 2015</title>
      <link>/posts/2014/2014-nov-25-frc-kickoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2014/2014-nov-25-frc-kickoff/</guid>
      <description>FRC Kickoff - Saturday, January 3, 2015 FRC Kickoff marks the beginning of the design and build season. Teams have the opportunity to meet at &amp;ldquo;local&amp;rdquo; Kickoffs to compare notes, get ideas, make friends, find mentoring teams, learn the game, pick up the Kit of Parts, and get geared up for the exciting competition season.
To find more information on the calendar competitions, facts for teams, surrogate kit pickup information, and more, visit usfirst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BunnyBots 2014</title>
      <link>/posts/2014/2014-dec-1-bunnybots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2014/2014-dec-1-bunnybots/</guid>
      <description>BunnyBots 2014 The annual BunnyBots competition is one of the highlights of the FRC off-season for 24 teams in the NW. It expands the boundaries of the 6-week build season to help make FIRST more of a year-round activity.
See more at Bunny Bots website: Copyright © 2014 · Oregon FIRST Robotics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Announcements</title>
      <link>/posts/2014/2014-sep-21-recent-announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2014/2014-sep-21-recent-announcements/</guid>
      <description>Recent Announcements Stormbots Information Meeting StormBots Information Meeting Wednesday 9/24/14, 7:00-8:00 pm600 Wing (You can enter through 600 wing side door, from the teacher&amp;rsquo;s parking lot off of&amp;hellip;
 Posted Sep 21, 2014, 11:35 AM by Kim Hansen
 Untitled Post The StormBots will be in this year’s 2014 Mini-makers faire at OMSI in Portland! On Saturday September 13th and Sunday September 14th the StormBots will be manning a booth at the Mini-maker fair alongside team 1540, The Flaming Chickens, and team&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competition Season Overview</title>
      <link>/posts/2014/2014-may-22-competition-season-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2014/2014-may-22-competition-season-overview/</guid>
      <description>Competition Season Overview We competed in the Oregon City competition. We had some problems with our robot in the first few qualification matches, but the team worked together to solve them. After improving in the next few matches, we were selected to be on an alliance. Unfortunately, we lost our first semifinal round and were eliminated from the competition. We finished in 25th place out of 35 teams! Overall, we are proud of our efforts as a team and plan to do even better in our Wilsonville competition this weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skyview StormBots Sponsor Night Will Be Rescheduled Due to Weather.</title>
      <link>/posts/2014/2014-feb-5-2014-sponsor-night-reschedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2014/2014-feb-5-2014-sponsor-night-reschedule/</guid>
      <description>Skyview StormBots Sponsor Night Will Be Rescheduled Due to Weather. ~Thursday, February 6, 2014~</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subteam Updates</title>
      <link>/posts/2014/2014-feb-2-subteam-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2014/2014-feb-2-subteam-updates/</guid>
      <description>Subteam Updates Controls
 Right now, we are setting up the motor controls so they are ready to be put on the board. This week, we hope to mount all the electronics on the board. So far, we have put the fans and fan guards on the motor controls.
 Research and Design
 We are finishing up detailing our CAD drawings to give to fabrication. This week, we hopefully will get the driving system, the claw, and the shooter done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls&#39; Generation 2012</title>
      <link>/posts/2012/2012-oct-14-girls-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2012/2012-oct-14-girls-generation/</guid>
      <description>Girls&amp;rsquo; Generation 2012 The StormBots finished on the 2nd place alliance!
Congratulations to Laurel, Tori, Becca, Matty and Sara!
We want to thank the volunteers and parents who helped make this event a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congradulations!</title>
      <link>/posts/2012/2012-mar-12-autodesk-oregion-regional/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2012/2012-mar-12-autodesk-oregion-regional/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations! The StormBots tied for 3rd place at the 2012 Seattle FIRST Regional Competition!
Competition was held at CenturyLink Field in Seattle. The StormBots won the Entrepreneur Award and a Pit Safety Award signed by Dean Kamen!
Way to go StormBots!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robotics Story from March 10 at the 2012 Autodesk Oregon Regional Competition</title>
      <link>/posts/2012/2012-mar-10-autodesk-regional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2012/2012-mar-10-autodesk-regional/</guid>
      <description>Robotics Story from March 10 at the 2012 Autodesk Oregon Regional Competition  Written by: Jason Vilaysanh
 Sitting in the cheering crowd, anticipation flows through my body; the FRC Team 2811 Skyview Stormbot 4, affectionately nicknamed the “Linfiltrator 2811” after the basketball player Jeremy Lin, was about to compete. Amongst the rest of the audience at the 2012 Autodesk Oregon Regional, I cry out in excitement and joy. It would be our time to shine: we would show everyone what the outcome of our hard work would be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portland and Seattle regionals Preparations</title>
      <link>/posts/2012/2012-jan-15-portland-and-seattle-regionals-preperations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2012/2012-jan-15-portland-and-seattle-regionals-preperations/</guid>
      <description>Portland and Seattle regionals Preparations We decided to build two robots this year for the Seattle and Portland regionals. That way, when it&amp;rsquo;s time to bag and tag the robot, we can continue working on the twin, looking for other problems to tweak. We made a shooter mechanism that is unique because it utilizes a rotating wheel to propel the ball ferociously but accurately. Our team also decided to program our robot to score points in autonomous mode, meaning the robot can score by itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Our Team! (2012)</title>
      <link>/posts/2012/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2012/text/</guid>
      <description>Meet Our Team Mentors Basil Zhabko:  I work for Columbia Ultimate, and I am Senior Software Engineer. This will be second season I have mentored for robotics. I like robotics because it is all about learning and knowledge sharing. I mentor for programming, and Competitive Intelligence sub-teams.
 Craig Boezwinkle:  I work for Western Integrated Technologies in Portland. We primarily build and sell hydraulic, pneumatic, and automation systems and components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BunnyBots 2011</title>
      <link>/posts/2011/2011-dec-18-bunnybot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2011/2011-dec-18-bunnybot/</guid>
      <description>BunnyBots 2011 20 teams attended this year&amp;rsquo;s BunnyBot. Of those 20 teams, our Skyview robotics team took 11th Place in the final standings. Many of the team members who participated either worked on the robot (build team), asked other teams how they raise money (marketing team), and/or drove the robot (drive team). Our drivers were Misha, Kelson, Connor, and Thomas. At BunnyBot each team was pared up with another team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stormbots Volunteer at  the Intel Oregon FIRST LEGO League Tournament</title>
      <link>/posts/2011/2011-dec-5-lego-league-tournament/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2011/2011-dec-5-lego-league-tournament/</guid>
      <description>Stormbots Volunteer at the Intel Oregon FIRST LEGO League Tournament Over 300 students between the ages of 9 and 14 participated in the FLL Robotics tournament at Salmon Creek Elementary. December 3 - 4. Skyview stormbots helped organize and judge the competition involving Lego robots from over 40 teams. The team demonstrated its 2011 competition robot to inspire the younger students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The StormBots Sparkle at Girls Generation</title>
      <link>/posts/2011/the-stormbots-sparkle-at-girls-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2011/the-stormbots-sparkle-at-girls-generation/</guid>
      <description>The StormBots Sparkle at Girls Generation Remember remember the 13th of November!
On Saturday the thirteenth, the &amp;ldquo;pretty in pink&amp;rdquo; side of the Stormbot&amp;rsquo;s team paraded to Catlin Gable for the first Pacific Northwest Girl&amp;rsquo;s Generation. Thirteen female robotics teams strutted their stuff with last seasons robots on the Breakaway field. Skyview&amp;rsquo;s girls sported hot pink shirts and comprised the largest group of girls of any team. The girls played an exciting game and even scored three goals in a 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StormBots Dominate at Girls Generation 2011</title>
      <link>/posts/2011/2011-oct-29-girls-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2011/2011-oct-29-girls-generation/</guid>
      <description>StormBots Dominate at Girls Generation 2011 Skyview robotics team girls&amp;ndash;Leslie, Becca, Madeline, Lauren, Zoey, and Hsuan-Ting—took the team’s competition robot from last season to Catlin Gable School on October 29 for the 2nd Annual girls-only “Girls Generation Robotics Competition.” This competition hopes to inspire girls to take advantage of the opportunities through FIRST Robotics to get “hands-on” experience with technology. It gives them a slight “leg up” over their often more domineering male counterparts, and a chance to witness the fun of engineering for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capture the Bunny 2nd Place</title>
      <link>/posts/2010/capture-the-bunny-2nd-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2010/capture-the-bunny-2nd-place/</guid>
      <description>Capture the Bunny 2nd Place A solid team effort captures 2nd place at the 2010 BunnyBot competition at Catlin Gable School in Portland. Carrying over the pink theme in shirt design, the team&amp;rsquo;s robust design, flawless programming and outstanding team work enabled them to survive 8 bolt-rattling rounds to make it to the championship finale.
Other robots were knocked over or had large and small pieces of their &amp;lsquo;bots fly off during intense clashes during play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StormBots Strike at 2010 PDX Regional</title>
      <link>/posts/2010/stormbots-strike-at-2010-pdx-regional/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2010/stormbots-strike-at-2010-pdx-regional/</guid>
      <description>March was the final countdown! The robotics build season amounted up to one peaking moment, the Autodesk Oregon Regional FIRST competition at the Memorial Coliseum. 30 hours of competition over three days were jam packed with spirited teams sporting their colors, mascots dancing to the Macarena, and robots in action battling it out on the field. A total of 104 fierce rounds were played, each consisting of 3 teams on a red alliance and 3 on a blue alliance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games/</guid>
      <description>First Power Up: 2018  Teams are required to place power cubes on scales and switches to gain ownership. Alliances can also trade power cubes for power ups, giving them a temporary advantage in the game. At the end of the game, robots can climb the tower to defeat the boss.             First Steamworks: 2017  Teams are required to shoot fuel into a boiler which generates steam for the airship in the middle of the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media/</guid>
      <description>PHOTO!   VIDEO!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calendar/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact The Stormbots</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>           Follow Us On Twitter/        Follow Us On Instagram/        Like Us On Facebook/        Email Us At info@stormbots.com        Subscribe On YouTube/        Visit Us On GitHub/        Our Schools Website/        Our District Website/        FIRST Robotics Website/       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Aerial Assist: 2014</title>
      <link>/aerial_assist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aerial_assist/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Breakaway: 2010</title>
      <link>/breakaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/breakaway/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Logomotion: 2011</title>
      <link>/logomotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/logomotion/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Power Up: 2018</title>
      <link>/power_up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/power_up/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Rebound Rumble: 2012</title>
      <link>/rebound_rumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rebound_rumble/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Recycle Rush: 2015</title>
      <link>/recycle_rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recycle_rush/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Steamworks: 2017</title>
      <link>/steamworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/steamworks/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Stronghold: 2016</title>
      <link>/stronghold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stronghold/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST Ultimate Ascent: 2013</title>
      <link>/ultimate_ascent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ultimate_ascent/</guid>
      <description>Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game. Text about our time in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/</guid>
      <description>VPS, because i need a test subject            Vancouver Public Schools     2008-2018        Providing both financial support as well as the literal roof over our heads. And there&amp;#39;s the whole education thing, which is kind of a big deal. 2015 sponsors, also for a test             Platt Electric Supply   Vancouver, WA   2008-2018        Electrical supply chain with a wide range of products including generators, lighting, tools &amp;amp; fuses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>